{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Architectural dimensioning standards allow for the placement of dimensions inside the floor plan. These inside dimensions locate interior ________.", "opta": "door openings and walls", "optb": "centers of cabinets", "optc": "windows", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When dimensioning architectural drawings architects will utilize both ________ and ________ options.", "opta": "Baseline and continuous", "optb": "Baseline and linear", "optc": "Quick dim and linear", "optd": "Linear and continuous", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Architectural dimensioning is usually done in ________.", "opta": "Even numbers", "optb": "Feet and inches", "optc": "Feet only", "optd": "Inches only", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Some of the standard AutoCAD text styles used in architectural drawings includes ________.", "opta": "CityBlueprint", "optb": "CountryBlueprint", "optc": "Stylus BT", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Dimension text is generally placed above the ________ line.", "opta": "Dimension", "optb": "extension", "optc": "center", "optd": "leader", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The architectural and construction industries use the United States National CAD standard (NCS) system on many ________ projects.", "opta": "residential", "optb": "commercial", "optc": "aerospace", "optd": "publicly funded", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "There should be a visible gap between the wall and the ________ line.", "opta": "dimension", "optb": "extension", "optc": "center", "optd": "leader", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Dimensions are used on the elevation plan to describe ________.", "opta": "Finished floor elevations", "optb": "Roof overhangs", "optc": "Roof pitch angles", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The second line of dimensions out from the plan generally includes ________.", "opta": "Centers of doors and windows", "optb": "The distances between outside walls and interior walls.", "optc": "The measurement from the outside of the brick to the inside of the exterior wall.", "optd": "The measurement from one outside corner to the opposite outside corner.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The dimension text size is determined by what the architect deems necessary in ________.", "opta": "Model space", "optb": "Paper space", "optc": "The Finished plot", "optd": "The PDF file", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}